來啊，給 Trixie 點顏色看看
C'mon, show Trixie what you've got
我是個魔法婊子
Imma magic bitch
你幹不死我
you can't kill me
我是個魔法婊子
Imma magic bitch
你打不亂我的節奏
you can't kill my vibe
你也想爬到我的位子？
And if you think you can reach me
你最好去把眼睛揉一揉
You wipe your own dirt out your eyes
噢，給我等一會兒
Oh, now wait a minute
我是不是恍神
I think I'm tripping
昨晚你說要算你一起
Last night you said you were in it
結果轉眼間就打倆退堂鼓
Next moment you're taking two steps back
一步一步
Hoof by hoof
你是不是跟我心結
you're a knot in my back
而且大家都說
And the consensus says
（嘿、嘿、嘿、嘿）
(yeah yeah yeah yeah)
你是個機掰人
You're a motherfucker
全家都做木工
coming out the woodwork
我竟然得自己爭取可愛標誌
Didn't know I had to earn my cutie mark
我真他媽抱歉
I'm so damn sorry
打從心底抱歉
from the bottom of my heart
我是個魔法婊子
And I'm a magic bitch
你沒話語權
you don't get a say
你就他媽給我滾一邊
Just move out the motherfucking way
你昨晚還在夢想今天
Last night you were dreaming bout today
我是個魔法婊子
And I'm a magic bitch
你就是替罪鬼
and you're the one to blame
才紅 20 秒鐘，給我滾開
Fuck off your 20 seconds of fame
現在他媽竟然在求我別走
suddenly you're asking me to fucking stay
T w l i 啜一口茶
T w l i sippin' that tea
我把世界弄到為我中心
I got the world spinnin' round me
我就是大姐頭
I’m that 4 OG
你以為我有時間
Gurl you think I got time
可憐小妹你
for your sad pity
賤貨，我他媽有個皇冠
Bitch I got fuckin' crown
還有文憑
and a PhD
別搗亂
Stop messing
我他媽不想管你
I’m fuckin' over that shit
你猜猜
You guessing
你他媽給我冷靜
Just sit yo ass down a bit
我是天使
Imma blessing
咱都知道我已經處理完了
Y’all know I'm done with this bit
你就愛鬧
So you're aggressive
你猜怎？你們，幹你們的
You know, y'all, fuck y'all
我要滾了，我滾
I'm out of here, I'm out
完—完—完—完—完美
P-p-p-p-perfect
我們活著最好的人生
We're living our lives to the fullest
難怪你一直在彌補
No wonder you've been making up
因為你很嫉妒
cuz you're jealous
你急需一個方針
You're in need of a plot to plot
心對心，你太用心了
Heart to heart, you're overzealous
因為我是個魔法婊子
Cuz I'm a magic bitch
你幹不死我
you can't kill me
你他媽屁都不管
You didn't give a shit
直到我變得小氣
till I started being bitty
耗的全都是我時間
And it's all on my fucking time
兩塊，三塊
2 bits, 3 bits
就為了押韻
for a fucking rhyme
我可以給我學生撥時間，但給你？
I can give a moment for my students, but for you?
我寧可跑去種花
I'd rather water Phyllis
因為我很多汁
Cuz I'm succulent
而你就是白痴
And you're opulent
而你說你想要學習點友誼
And you say you wanna learn a bit about friendship
你說你很誠實，所以你就一直噴糞
Saying that you're honest, so you keep on spewing horse shit
對我不公平
It's not fair to me
對其他人也是
everypony too
只在乎優先級
Priority in check
我是個壞婊子
Cuz I'm a bad bitch
你幹不死我
you can't kill me
（我是個壞婊子）
(Cuz I'm a bad bitch)
（你幹不死我）
(you can't kill me)
而你是個瘋婆子
And you're a mad bitch
你不懂我
you don't know me
（而你是個瘋婆子）
(And you're a mad bitch)
（你不懂我）
(you don't know me)
我是個壞婊子
Cuz I'm a bad bitch
你幹不死我
you can't kill me
因為那就是我跟我朋友的魔法
Cuz that's the magic I've got for myself and my friends